（忆往昔）
你是什么
So you're a what?
英格兰的记录者吗
You're, uh, English Men of Letters?
不列颠
‭British.
我们想跟你们合作
We wanna work with you.
- 米克吧 - 我的号码
- Uh, Mick, is it? - My number.
怎么样
What do we think?
要相信英国佬那套「我们做朋友吧」的话吗
Are we buying that Brit's whole "Let's be friends" routine?
不可能
No. No way.
温家兄弟 他们不比他们控制不了的
The Winchesters are no better than the monsters.
那些怪物强到哪去
they fail to control.
他们该被铲除
They need to be eliminated.
那种事可以留给凯奇先生
Well, we have Mr. Ketch for that.
我收拾了温家兄弟留下的麻烦
I cleaned up the Winchesters' mess.
我们猜中了 他们没能完成任务
As suspected, they couldn't finish the job.
谢谢你 凯奇先生
Thank you, Mr. Ketch.
你的晚餐男伴多金 单身
Your dinner date is loaded, single,
很可能还有健康问题
and possibly in delicate health.
这是我抛下
It's my chance to leave behind.
怪物 恶魔和潮湿藏身处的机会
monsters and demons and moldy hideouts.
路西法 皮囊是文斯·文森特
Lucifer wearing Vince Vincente.
你…还算有名
You're…kind of famous.
勇往直前
Onward and upward.
所以他才一个个地换皮囊
That's why he's jumping from vessel to vessel.
找到他就是我的责任
Me finding him is my responsibility.
小卡 你会需要支援的
Cass, you're gonna want some backup on this.
但如果你们困住了路西法 需要帮助
If you get Lucifer cornered and find yourself in need,
我会去的
I'm there.
小卡跟克劳力搭伙了
Cass is chumming it up with Crowley.
他们在一起追踪路西法
They're hunting Lucifer together.
毛毛和我都难舍难分了
Feathers and I are all but inseparable.
又一起了
Together again.
真棒
Yay.
（如今）
因为前所未见的干旱
And in the unprecedented drought condition…
本州农民担心
farmers in the state worry that.
来年的作物将全部颗粒无收
the entirety of next year's crop could be lost,
这促使了世界范围内的涨价
driving up prices worldwide.
另一则新闻
In other news,
警方在调查亿万富翁和慈善家
police are investigating the mysterious death.
华莱士·帕克的神秘死亡
of billionaire philanthropist Wallace Parker.
帕克上周二被发现死于办公室中
Parker was found dead in his office late Tuesday,
- 他的尸体严重受损 - 关掉
- his body heavily damaged… - Turn that off.
似乎遭遇了爆炸
by an explosion of some ki…
我们最好还是专注于主的事务
Better we stay focused on the Lord's work.
不是吗
Wouldn't you agree?
当然 阁下
Of course, Your Excellency.
帕克先生的事真是遗憾
Such a shame about Mr. Parker.
我知道他是您朋友
I know he was a friend.
更不用说还是我们最大的资助人之一
Not to mention, one of our biggest donors.
是啊
Yes.
[邪恶力量 第12季第8集]
你们的同事已经到了
Your colleagues are already inside.
- 探员 - 探员
- Agents. - Agents.
行了 这真是够了
Okay, this has gotta stop.
给我
All right, give me that.
- 阿玛尼的 - 行了
- Armani! - Okay, enough.
我们看看吧
Let's have a look.
某人忘记擦防晒霜了
Looks like somebody forgot to put on his sunscreen.
这是华莱士·帕克
This was Wallace Parker,
几乎执行总裁了一切 很有势力
the very powerful CEO of almost everything.
看来 也是路西法的最新一具皮囊
And apparently, Lucifer's latest vessel.
但不足以支撑住他
Wasn't strong enough to hold him.
路西法不满足于
Lucifer's not content with slutting it.
一具具地换普通皮囊
from one random vessel to the next.
他开始选绩优股了
He's moving on to blue chips …
名人 业内领袖
celebrities, captains of industry.
他变得更加危险了
He just got a lot more dangerous.
我同意扎帕探员的看法
I agree with Agent Zappa.
你够了吧
Oh, will you stop?
有发现吗
So, find anything?
有哪位有权有势的人
Anyone powerful or respectable.
突然画风大变 或爆炸了吗
who suddenly changed… or exploded?
这个挺有趣
Well, this is pretty interesting.
这位是圣路易斯的大主教
This is the Archbishop of St. Louis.
跟华莱士·帕克的合照
with Wallace Parker.
- 怎么了 - 这是三天前的他
- So? - So that was him three days ago.
这
And this…
是昨晚的他 在一家施粥场开幕式上
is him last night at the opening of a food kitchen.
发现少了什么吗
Notice anything missing?
嗯 老大个的那个十字架
Yeah, the big mother of a cross around his neck.
没错 今早
Exactly. And this morning,
他的办公室取消了所有其他公共活动
his office canceled all further public appearances.
且未作出解释
without comment.
好吧 你觉得
Okay, so you're thinking that, uh,
路西法从帕克出来
Lucifer blasted out of Parker.
进入了他的朋友大主教体内
and into his buddy the Archbishop here.
- 值得一试 - 嗯
- Worth a shot. - Yeah.
（圣路易斯大主教区）
好安静
It's awfully quiet.
是啊 我给办公室主任打了好几通电话
Yeah, I put in a dozen calls to the Chief of Staff.
没人接
No one returned.
我们去看看
Well, we'll have a look around.
如果是路西法 再把其他人叫来
If it is Lucifer, we'll call the rest of the Scooby gang.
这可好
Great.
神父
Father, hey.
怎么回事
What happened?
我们就觉得不对劲
We… knew something was wrong.
他…
He… he…
大主教
The Archbishop?
高级职员决定
Senior staff decided…
内部解决
handle internally.
进行干涉
and intervene.
驱魔
An exorcism.
如果我同意了
If I agree to this,
我们就是搭档
we would be partners.
为美国带来真正的灵性时代
We would bring a true era of spirituality to America.
治愈它的创伤
and heal her wounds?
那哈利路亚
Then hallelujah.
我恭敬地接受你的指引
I humbly accept your guidance.
好
Yes.
太好了
Swell.
现在呢
Now what?
好了 杰夫
Okay, then, Jeff.
我一般会给我的宿主更多休息时间
Usually, I give my hosts more downtime,
但这次 就高调行事吧
but in this case, high-profile as it is…
我可能需要帮助调整一些…规程
I may need help fine-tuning some…protocols.
这样我才能做到我所承诺的
if I'm going to deliver on all the goodness.
那些善事和公共服务
and public service that I promised.
我很乐意帮忙 搭档
I'm … I'm happy to help, partner.
我们要在这里参加一系列筹款活动
We're appearing at … at a series of fundraisers here.
有一群很棒的助理在帮我们
backed by a fantastic group of aides.
我只需要关注大局喽
So I just focus on the big picture?
由团队处理细节问题
The team handles the details.
听着 杰夫
Well, listen, Jeff,
这些消息是非常有用
this is all useful information, of course.
但是 如果我们想做好
But…if we're gonna pull this off,
我需要更多私人细节
I'm gonna need a few more personal details.
人们需要相信我就是
People need to believe that I am, in fact,
美国总统
President of the United States.
前一刻我们还在探讨最好的烤肉
One minute, we're talking about the best barbecue.
我喜欢堪萨斯城
I'm a Kansas City man.
比尔喜欢孟菲斯
Bill likes Memphis.
我去了厕所
I stepped into the john.
出来时 他已经倒地了
When I came out, he was on the ground.
我给他做了心肺复苏
I, uh, I tried CPR, but, uh…
我相信您已经尽力了 先生
I'm sure you did everything you could, Sir,
但他似乎是发生了严重的脑出血
but it appears he had a massive cerebral hemorrhage.
我们得做尸检
We're gonna need an autopsy,
但我看不出谋杀的迹象
but I don't see any evidence of foul play.
您想说两句吗 先生
If you'd like to say a few words, Sir.
对天上的那位说两句 先生
A few words to the man upstairs, Sir,
就像您每天早晨那样
like you do every morning.
当然
Yes.
说两句
Words.
我们无论说什么似乎都不够
Nothing we ever say feels like enough.
孩子
Babies.
我们就是孩子
That's what we are.
无辜
Innocents.
我们都在努力
All of us struggling to…
正直行事 目标明确 充满骄傲
walk upright with purpose and … and pride.
但我们需要「天父」
And yet, we need "Our Father"…
来
to…
接住摔倒的我们
be there when we fall.
今天 我们失去了一个兄弟
Today, we lost a brother.
明天 我们将继续为国效力
Tomorrow, we will continue our work for the country.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
你总是知道该说什么
You always know the right thing to say.
这些照片
These pictures…
如此的暴力 根本没必要
The level of violence, it's completely unnecessary.
路西法不喜欢别人招惹他
Lucifer doesn't like to get messed with.
我猜当大主教手下的牧师
I guess when the Archbishop's priests.
发现他被附身后
figured out he was possessed,
他们想低调处理 自己驱魔
they tried to keep it quiet, do an exorcism.
虽然本来也不会好使
I mean, not that it would've worked.
路西法离开了
Lucifer blew town,
但还是先杀了所有人
but not before he slaughtered the entire staff.
所以我们查对了 但他现在去哪了
So we were on the right trail. Where's it go now?
我不知道
I don't know.
谁赢了诺贝尔和平奖 我们从那儿查起吧
Who won the Nobel Peace Prize? Why don't we start there?
（福斯特庄园 总统宅院）
我们不在华府期间 白俄罗斯那边
While we've been away from from D.C., in Belaurus,
叛军和政府的谈判
negotiations between rebel forces and the government.
失败了
have broken down.
我们要把哈肯大使召回来
We're recalling Ambassador Harkin.
先生 是不是该让联合国插手了
Sir, is it time to involve the U.N.?
或者 我们可以直接一个核弹轰了他们
That or we can just go ahead and nuke 'em.
好吧 2点有蒙特罗伊筹款活动
Well! Montroy fundraiser at 2:00.
晚餐时再说吧
We'll pick this up at dinner.
先生
Sir.
您可能想知道 新民调结果已经出来了
Thought you might want to know, the new poll numbers are out.
您支持率很高
You're way up.
是近代以来最受欢迎的在任总统
Officially the most popular sitting President in modern history.
是嘛
Really?
不错啊
That's impressive.
奥图
Uh, Otto…
去休息一下
take a little break.
还有什么事吗
Was there something else?
太棒了
So amazing.
是啊
Yeah.
就好像我从来没做过
It's almost like I've never done that before.
你…
You…
杰夫 我得承认
You know, Jeff, I admit…
保密还挺刺激的
it makes things kind of exciting keeping this a secret.
我只希望
I just wish.
我们可以把对彼此的感觉
we could make how we feel about each other…
公诸于众
well, public.
我知道
I know…
大家可能不会赞同的
people might not like it.
因为你是鳏夫 公众可能不会接受
Public might not like it because you're a widower.
但是
But…
我知道露易丝死后你一直很寂寞
I know you've been lonely since Louise died.
我也知道你对我的感情是真的
And I know your feelings for me are real,
因为你做的一切都是真诚的
because everything you do is real.
我只是想认为
I just love to think that…
有一天
someday…
我们可以成为真正的一对儿
we could be a real couple.
或许结个婚
Maybe do the wedding thing.
或许生个孩子
Maybe the baby thing.
我就是…
I just…
我知道你肯定会成为个好父亲
I just know you'd make an amazing father.
好姑娘 真准时
Good girl. You're right on time.
陛下
Your majesty.
继续这么听话 你或许真能把灵魂赎回去
Keep this up and you could actually earn back your soul.
今天有什么消息告诉我
What little tidbit do you have for me today?
昨晚有一起死亡被我判为自然死亡 但…
There was a death last night that I ascribed to natural causes, but…
那绝对不是自然的
it was anything but natural.
地堡的符文坏掉了吗
Did the Bunker's warding fail?
我关掉了它
I just powered it down.
克劳力打来了 说有关于路西法的重要消息
Crowley called, said he had some big news about Lucifer,
谁知道是什么意思
whatever the hell that means.
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait a second.
克劳力现在
So … so now Crowley can just…what,
可以想来就来了吗
drop in whenever he feels like it?
我更想跟克劳力保持距离 远距离
I-I prefer keeping Crowley at a distance. Long distance.
真冷漠啊 小鹿
Not very charitable, Moose…
尤其 我又再一次
…particularly since, once again,
要救你们俩
I'm saving both your asses.
各位知道
So, as you know,
我暂时不能回我的宫殿
I'm temporarily persona non grata in my own palace.
- 宫殿 - 宫殿
- Palace? - Palace?
但是 还有些人依然受我控制 我的特工
However, there are those I still control. Operatives.
克劳力 能不能有事说事 别装逼了
Crowley, can we just get the damn news without the drama?
那你能不穿法兰绒吗
Can I get you without the flannel?
不能 但我不也忍了吗
No. Still, I endure.
干什么
What?
我根据一条线索 做了点调查
Did a little digging, acting on a tip.
我认为 我知道路西法最新皮囊是谁了
And I think I know the identity of Lucifer's newest vessel.
老天爷啊
Oh, for God's sake.
先生们
Gentlemen…
这位是杰夫森·鲁尼
I give you one Jefferson Rooney,
美国总统
President of these United States.
您找我 先生
You wanted to see me, Sir?
里克 出了点急事
Rick, something urgent's come up.
紧急 而且机密
Urgent and…confidential.
了解
Understood.
有可靠情报显示
We have reliable intel.
两个精神不稳定的人
that two mentally unstable individuals,
可能是邪教成员
possibly cult members,
准备在这几天里刺杀我
have imminent plans to assassinate me.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
因为我是撒旦
Because I'm Satan.
他们认为我是撒旦
They think I'm Satan.
不是比喻性的吗
Not metaphorically?
撒旦本人
In the flesh.
撒旦不是真的
Satan's not real.
- 这个嘛… - 他是傻瓜想出来的符号
- Well… - He's a symbol for the simple-minded.
漫画书里的恶人
A-a comic book villain.
对很多人来说 他有更多意义 里克
He's a bit more than that, Rick, to many people.
这事我并不知情
I wasn't briefed on this.
我这不就告诉你了吗
Well, I'm briefing you now.
我们之前一直没有动作 等待更多消息
We've been sitting on it until we had more facts.
除了对我有明显的威胁
Aside from the obvious peril to me…
我们会完全保密的 先生
We'll keep it strictly under the radar, Sir.
我觉得最好的方式就是消灭威胁
I think the best way to do that is to eliminate the threat.
不是吗
Would you agree?
我们可以启动审批流程
We could initiate the approval process.
不 不
No. No.
这事我们得内部解决
We need to handle this in the family.
只限特勤局插手
Secret Service only.
作为我个人安保队的队长
And as the head of my personal detail,
你要亲自带队处理
you will head this up yourself.
当然
Of course.
我喜欢这份工作 里克
I'm liking this job, Rick.
我想尽量多做一会儿
I wanna keep it a while.
（米克·戴维斯）
你好 我是米克·戴维斯
Hello. Mick Davies here.
请留言
Leave a mess…
就算克劳力真找来了罗威娜 问题依旧
Even if Crowley does bring in Rowena, the problem remains.
路西法在皮囊里时不能被锁回笼子里
Lucifer can't be returned to the cage inside his vessel.
得提取出他的精华
His essence has to be extracted.
是啊 而且路西法找到了完美的安全屋
Yeah. And Lucifer has found the perfect safe house.
我们要怎么接近总统啊
I mean, how do we even start getting close to the President?
幸好他不在华府
Well, it helps that he's not in D.C.
他在中西部进行巡回筹款呢
Well, he's, uh, actually on a fundraising swing through the Midwest.
是啊 看来他的整队人马
Yeah, right now, it looks like his whole party …
助理 特勤局 所有人
aides, Secret Service, the whole circus …
都住在罗恩·福斯特的一处宅邸
is staying at an estate owned by Ron Forester,
是一个对冲基金亿万富翁
the, uh, hedge fund zillionaire.
就在印第安纳波利斯城外
It's right outside Indianapolis.
但那里被高墙 安保人员 特勤局
But it is completely surrounded by walls, security,
和军队层层包围
Secret Service, military.
B计划呢
Plan B?
他有好多演讲安排
He's got a hell of a speaking schedule.
每天平均三次活动
He's averaging three events a day,
周五晚还有晚宴
and he's got a gala dinner on Friday night.
至少他会离开别墅
Well, at least he'll be outside of the mansion.
但同时像希望钻石一样被护得周周全全
Yeah, guarded like the Hope Diamond.
C计划呢
Plan C?
那我们呢 我们对彼此的感情呢
What about us? Our … our feelings for each other?
所以我对莫娜的事完全坦白
That's why I've been totally up front about Mona.
莫娜
Mona?
莫娜·莱文
Mona Levin.
Mona Levin?
那个女继承人
The heiress?
你还跟她约会了
You've been seen her as well?!
你知道人总得多些选择
You know one has to keep one's options open.
心意是控制不住的
The heart knows what the heart knows.
你对我的心意呢
And what does your heart know about me?
我喜欢你
It knows that it's fond of you.
但你的资历都无法查证
But your credentials were unverifiable.
金融控股 皇家芭蕾 都无法核实
Financial holdings, Royal Ballet, none of it!
你还调查我了
You had me investigated?!
你在骗我
You were scamming me!
好个五十步笑百步
Oh, there's the pot calling the kettle black.
可算来了
Finally.
少上浆
Light starch.
我向一个穷光蛋敞开了心扉
I offered my heart to a pauper.
你根本就是想要我不存在的财产
who was after my nonexistent fortune!
我也是一样 亲爱的 我不过是挑明了
Same as I did, sweetie. I'm just being honest about it.
- 这是谁 - 我最新的未婚夫
- Who is this? - My latest fiancé.
如果我把真相告诉莫娜呢
And if I tell Mona the truth?
那会是头一遭了
That'd be a first.
- 滚 - 这是我家
- Get out! - It's my place!
母亲
Mother.
「母亲」
"Mother"?
这是你为我做过的最好的事
That is the sweetest thing you've ever done for me.
保证你不会笑
Promise you won't laugh.
哪怕很好笑
Even if it's funny?
我不笑
I won't laugh.
今晚 我们俩 感觉
Tonight, us here, it felt…
不一样
different.
这下我真不想笑了
Now I'm really not laughing.
不是
No.
我们还是很棒 但是
We were great, as always, but…
不知怎么
somehow…
我描述不上来
in some way I can't describe,
但感觉
it feels like…
好像有什么变了
something's changed.
或许是有什么变了
Maybe something has.
小卡 小卡
Cass? Cass?
出事了
Something's happened. Something…
天使电台 有好多声音
Angel radio… There are so many voices.
都说什么呢
What are they saying?
天堂能量出现了强烈涌动
There's been a massive surge in celestial energy.
一个拿非利人要诞生了
A nephilim is come into being.
就是天使和凡人的后代
It's the offspring of an angel and a human.
这是重大消息吗
And that's big news?
是的 造成这个的能量很大
Yes, but the power to produce this is immense.
比一般的天使厉害的多
It's much, much greater than a typical angel.
路西法
Lucifer.
W… Lucifer?
我都不知道他在约会
I didn't know he was dating.
（印第安纳波利斯）
嗯 克劳力
Yeah, and hey, Crowley?
跟你的政府内线问问
find out from your government mole if there's a.
他是否有女友 情妇或宠爱的妓女
girlfriend or a mistress or a favorite hooker.
我们不知道的人
Someone we don't know about.
知道了 好
Got it. All right.
克劳力和罗威娜会在印第安纳波利斯跟我们碰面
Crowley and Rowena will meet us in Indianapolis.
有计划了吗
Do we have a plan?
弹劾总统路西法 并找到魔鬼圣婴
Impeach LOTUS and find Rosemary's Baby.
该死
Aw, crap.
好了 待在这里 我们去
All right. Stay here. We got this.
先生们 有什么问题吗
Gentlemen, is there a problem?
我们是联邦探员 还得赶路呢
Federal Agents, guys. We need to keep going.
我周六前还得凑齐六千块呢 不照样没戏
And I need 6 grand by Saturday, but that ain't happening either.
你们知道我们是谁吗
You guys know who you're talking to?
温家兄弟
Winchesters.
假证是手工课上还是在精神病院里做的
You make those toy badges in craft class on the psyche ward?
车不错 非常显眼
Nice car, by the way. Really stands out.
等等
Wait a second now.
放了他 快点
Let him go. Now.
站住
Stop!
- 别动 - 小卡 别
- Don't move! - ‭Cass, don't.
你 天使 抹去他们的记忆
You. Angel. Wipe their memories.
美国政府牌照 精英猎狗人
U.S. Government plates. Elite dogcatcher level.
有特别的人想抓你们
Someone special wants you.
你们是招惹谁了
Whose hydrant have you lads been tinkling on?
对不起 你是谁
I'm sorry. Who the hell are you?
我太没礼貌了
Where are my manners?
亚瑟·凯奇 英国记录者
Arthur Ketch. British Men of Letters.
其实很简单的
So it's all very simple, really.
米克·戴维斯邀你们加入我们
Mick Davies asked you to join our effort,
我们打算进行国际化
which we're taking international.
我的指示是 好好激励你们答应
My instructions are to strongly encourage a "Yes."
怎么 你一直在跟踪我们吗
So, what? You've just been following us?
不是 我们是好狗 只有受召唤才会出现
Not at all. We're good dogs. We only come when called.
他打了电话
And he called.
你什么
You what?
我没有…
I-I didn't, uh…
我挂了
I hung up.
是啊
Yes, you did,
所以戴维斯先生认为你们有了麻烦
which made Mr. Davies think that you were in trouble,
他猜对了
which you were.
所以他打给了我 丁零当啷
So he rings me. Bing, bang, boom.
接下来就顺理成章了
Meet Bob. He's your uncle.
对了 不客气
Oh, and, um, you're welcome.
我们为什么要相信你的话
And why should we believe anything that you have to say?
你 光圈
You, Halo.
你觉得我在说谎吗
Do you sense I'm lying?
我叫卡西迪奥
My name is Castiel.
没有
And… no.
但真话有时要看情况
But the truth can be situational.
我就喜欢天使
I do enjoy an angel.
但我理解你们的迟疑
But I understand your hesitation.
你们并没有看到我们最好的一面
You haven't exactly seen us at our best.
贝维尔夫人有点 容易激动
Lady Bevell is a bit… excitable.
她企图杀我们
She tried to kill us.
- 我说了 容易激动 - 你就强点吗
- Like I said, excitable. - And you're better?
我既不喜欢你们 也不讨厌你们
I don't care about you one way or the other.
我不是空想家
I'm not an ideologue.
你只想帮助这对儿美国猎人
And all you wanna do is help these American Hunters.
清理这个国家的怪物
to clear this country of monsters?
我们理解这里的情况不一样
We understand things are different here.
我们愿意合作
We're eager to collaborate.
英国记录者有数世纪的历史 各位
The British Men of Letters are centuries old, lads.
我们可以提供专业知识
We can offer expertise,
武器 技艺
weaponry, skills.
就像刚刚那样的吗
Like we saw out on the road?
我是个艺术家 温彻斯特先生
I'm an artist, Mr. Winchester.
我用很多颜色作画
I paint in many colors.
刚刚那是枪榴弹发射器吗
Was that a grenade launcher?
是的
Quite.
我们的工程师花费数年
Our engineers have spent years.
融合巫术和科技
blending sorcery and technology.
比如 我们并不总砍吸血鬼的头
For instance, we don't always decapitate vampires.
不够高效 尤其是对大血巢
Inefficient, reallea especially for large nests.
我们辐射他们
We irradiate them,
改变他们的DNA
reorder their DNA.
让他们的血液变成致命毒物
Their own blood becomes lethal to them.
厉害
Cool.
玩具最好玩了 是吧
The toys are the fun part, hmm?
双曲线脉冲发生器
Hyperbolic Pulse Generator.
驱魔很不靠谱
Exorcisms are unreliable.
这件装置能放出一股力量
This device emits a force.
迫使附身的恶魔离开皮囊
which drives the possessing demon from the vessel.
那附身的天使呢
What about a, uh, possessing angel?
你们在追查什么呢
And what might you boys be working on?
你想要我们信任你 就得先信任我们
You want us to trust you, you're gonna have to trust us first.
什么意思
And that means?
你要用那个把路西法从总统身体里赶出去
So you're gonna pop Lucifer out of the President with that?
希望能行 否则我们死定了
I hope so. Otherwise, we're all dead.
然后让罗威娜把他送回笼子
Then Rowena zaps him back to the cage.
当然 我们得先把他弄来
Of course, we gotta get him here first.
是啊 我们得找到
Yeah. We need to get ahold of this,
克劳力查到的秘密女友
secret girlfriend Crowley found out about. This…
凯莉
Kelly.
当然了 她跟总统一起在别墅里
Of course, she's in that mansion with the President,
那里戒备森严
which is guarded like a fortress.
我们中只有一人有可能进得去
Only one of us has a chance of getting in there.
该死
Bollocks.
是的 我怀孕了
Yes, I'm pregnant.
我不知道什么时候 谢丽
I don't know when, Sheri.
也不知道怎么会 只知道我是怀了
I don't know how. I just know that I am.
你好 亲爱的
Hello, darling.
这会有点疼
This is going to sting a bit.
不不 你们骗人 这不可能
No, no, you're making it up. It's impossible.
不过 瞬移不也是不可能的吗
Well, to be fair, so is teleporting. But…
但你在这儿呢
ta-da.
你们是什么人
Who are you people?
亲爱的 我是个女巫
Well, dear, I'm a witch.
他是个天使
He's an angel.
我是地狱之王
And I'm the King of Hell.
上帝呐
Oh, God.
其实 他走了
No, actually, he left.
各位 帮倒忙呢
Okay, guys, not helping.
你不能 他是总统
You … you can't. He's the President.
他原来是 但现在
He was, but now…
难道他的行为没有变化吗
Tell me he hasn't been acting different.
杰夫最近压力很大
Jeff's been under a lot of stress. He…
不 他是魔鬼
Wrong. He's the Devil.
长角 干草叉 全套
Horns, pitchfork, the whole nine.
克劳力 还是帮倒忙
Crowley, still not helping.
听着 我们清楚自己在做什么
Listen, we know what we're talking about here.
我们查路西法很久了
We have been on Lucifer's trail for a long time.
我们知道你怀了他的孩子
And we know you're pregnant with his child.
你…你们撒谎
That's … that's … you're lying.
你体内的东西 是不洁的
The thing inside you, it's unholy.
是恶果
It's an abomination.
不…
That's n…
把手放在这里
Place your hand here.
不
No.
Oh, no. ‭
他知道你怀孕了吗
Does he even know you're knocked up?
是的
Yes, he…
他说他很激动
He said he was thrilled.
他说这是他唯一一次创造了什么
He said it was the only time he ever created anything.
凯莉
Kelly…
我们需要你帮忙
we need your help.
「我赦免…
"I grant a full pardon…"
查尔斯·曼森「
"…to Charles Manson."
凯莉
Kelly.
（平原旅馆）
先生 我们照您说的 只有小队人跟随
Sir, we agreed to keep this small like you asked.
我们现在进去 快速检查一下
We're gonna go inside, run a quick sweep.
好的
Absolutely.
可不希望我出事
Wouldn't want anything happening to me.
克莱恩小姐
Ms. Kline.
这里只有凯莉
There's no one in here but Kelly.
去车里等着
Go wait in your car.
安全
It's clear.
走吧
Let's go.
里面只有凯莉 我们在车里等着
There's no one in there but Kelly. We'll wait in the car.
凯莉
Kelly.
凯莉 怎么了
Kelly, what's wrong?
我在电话上跟你说了
I told you on the phone.
我不能把孩子生下来
I can't have this baby.
我恐怕要坚持
I'm afraid I'll have to insist.
萨姆
Sam.
[咒语]
这一套我们玩过那么多次了
We've done this dance so many times.
[咒语]
萨姆
Sam!
罗威娜 快
Rowena, now!
[咒语]
这事没完 萨姆
This isn't over, Sam!
下地狱去吧
Go to Hell!
[咒语]
他还活着 他什么都不会记得的
He's alive. He won't remember a thing.
杰夫 天呐
Jeff. Oh, my God.
杰夫
Jeff?
- 天呐 - 我们得走了
- Oh, my God. - We gotta go.
带她离开 快走
Get her out of here. Go.
凯莉 你得走了 快走
Kelly, you gotta go. Go.
我们抓到他了
We got him.
我们抓到路西法了
We got Lucifer.
总统先生
Mr. President?
好了 没事的 慢慢来 猛男
Okay. All right. Take it easy, Tiger.
总统先生
Mr. President!
站起来 手举过头顶
On your feet! Hands on your heads!
手举过头顶
‭Hands on your heads!
- 听着 我们是想 - 闭嘴
- Okay, listen, we were just trying to - ‭Shut up!
你们因企图行刺美国总统
You're under arrest for the attempted assassination.
被捕了
of the President of the United States.
对不起 我…需要点时间
I'm sorry. I just… I need a minute.
（女厕）
凯莉
Kelly.
凯莉 你没事吧
Kelly, are you all right?
凯莉
Kelly?
- 喂 - 卡西迪奥
- Hello? - Castiel…
我不能
I can't do it.
凯莉
Kelly.
我能感觉到它在我体内
I can feel it inside me.
我是它的母亲
I'm its mother.
凯莉 听我说 那不是个孩子
Kelly, you listen to me. This is not a baby.
那是路西法的后代
This is the spawn of Lucifer.
是我的孩子
It's my child.
不 凯莉 你…
No, no. Kelly, you…